Deliverable 4.5)
How many joints impact motion of the LEFT_FOOT relative to the RIGHT_FOOT? What would be the new size of your Jacobian Matrix?
	There are 6 joints that can impact motion. This would make the Jacobian into a 3X6 matrix as it needs to be compatible with a 6X1 α˙ column vector.

What kind of problems might this pose to performing resolved rate kinematics? How might using a pseudo-inverse help in this situation?
	This would of course require more computation when it comes to performing resolved rate inverse kinematics. We could be faced with a matrix that isn't invertible. The pseudoinverse would help in ensuring that we don't try to force the biped to go to a position that's outside its reachable workspace. Additionally, although we have not addressed the issue in the class, the real biped joints cannot perform full 2pi rotation, which reduces the reachable workspace further than we have considered in the Biped class. 

